in this video I'll teach you how to buy
an insurance online first you go to shop
dot FWD calm dot pH and then you can
choose one can do plan you want to
purchase
so there's can meant can live and can
guard so can man is for medical
treatment
its support for medical treatment and
its 1799 and then you have can live
which is like a life insurance so it's
also one thousand seven hundred ninety
nine per year and the last one is con
guard which is an accident insurance so
again it's one seven ninety nine in the
coverage is five hundred thousand cash
benefit so those are the differences of
the three con guard plans and in order
to get one you need to have a credit
card or debit card so I'll show you how
to actually purchase the insurance
online so I'm trying to buy the the con
guard which is the accident insurance so
I'm gonna put in my details yeah I just
put in my details I just cut it and then
you need to have a valid ID a copy of
your valid ID which you need to upload i
got an sss card so that's what i
uploaded and you can just click the
declarations yeah that you are not
working at some yeah just read it there
it's it's there
and click the completed application
button and then read the data privacy
declaration and once you read it you can
click that then you can now proceed to
paying your insurance plan again I got
the Conn guard because I travel a lot so
it gives me like a peace of mind
whatever happens I'm insured so again
that's 1799 and I'm paying by credit
card so they're after like few minutes
it's now ready yeah I've got the
insurance already I'm insured